WORAWIT TEPSAN

Contact: International College of Digital Innovation (ICDI),

Chiang Mai University (CMU), Chiang Mai, Thailand

Email: worawit.tepsan@cmu.ac.th, webpage: cmu.to/wtepsan

Profile: Lecturer at ICDI, Research Interests in Data Analysis, Machine Learning,

Artificial Intelligence, Digital Technology, and Applied Mathematics.



PUBLICATIONS

-	Shu H, Dawod A Y, Tepsan W, Mou L, Tang Z. Multi-channel Microseismic Signal Classification with Convolutional Neural	2023
	Networks, IAES International Journal of Artificial Intelligence (IJ-AI), (To be published in 2023)	

- Ran X, Zhou X, Lei M, Tepsan W, Deng W. A Novel K-Means Clustering Algorithm with a Noise Algorithm for Capturing
 Urban Hotspots. *Applied Sciences*. 2021; 11(23):11202. https://doi.org/10.3390/app112311202
- Blecher, D.P., Tepsan, W. Real Operator Algebras and Real Positive Maps. *Integr. Equ. Oper. Theory* 93, 49 (2021). 2021 https://doi.org/10.1007/s00020-021-02665-1

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCES

•	Research on Human Action Recognition Project using Skeleton Database with NECTEC	Jun 2022-Now
•	Training in Super AI Engineer Season Program organized by Artificial Intelligence Association of Thailand	Nov 2021-Aug 2022
	(AIAT) [certificate: https://aiat.or.th/cert/files/SuperAIEngineer2021/EN-SuperAI2-019.png]	
•	Training in Agricultural Data Scientist Program organized by Faculty of Science and Industrial Technology,	July 2022
	Prince of Songkla University, Surat Thani Campus	
•	Co-Researcher: The study of growth poles of the Northern Economic Corridor Project, Thailand	2021
	(Grant from the Ministry of Higher Education, Science, Research and Innovation, Thailand)	
•	PhD Thesis: Real Operator Spaces, Real Operator Algebras and Real Jordan Operator Algebras	2020
•	Master's degree Thesis: Triangular Mean-Value Functional Equation	2012
•	Senior Research: Algorithms for Solving Periodic Pentadiagonal Linear System and Inverting Periodic	2010
	Pentadiagonal Matrices	
	Mini Project: Algorithm for Finding Shortest path in Chiang Mai City	2008

EMPLOYMENT

•	Lecturer at International College of Digital Innovation, Chiang Mai University, Thailand	Dec 2020 - Current
•	Special Expert at International College of Digital Innovation, Chiang Mai University, Thailand	Aug 2020 - Dec2020
•	Teaching Assistance at University of Houston, TX, USA	2015- 2020
•	Tutor (Self Employed) for secondary and high school students in Math, BKK, Thailand	2010- 2013
•	Teaching assistance in Real Analysis (2010 term 1), Numerical Analysis (2010 term 2),	2010, 2012
	and Calculus (2012 summer) at Chulalongkorn University, BKK, Thailand	

EDUCATION

•	PhD in Mathematics from University of Houston, Texas, USA	2015-2020
•	Studied for PhD in Mathematics but then moved to University of Houston Ohio University, Ohio, USA (did not graduate)	2013-2015
•	Master of Science in Mathematics from Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok, Thailand	2010-2013
-	Bachelor of Science in Mathematics (Minor in Computer Science) from Chiang Mai University, Chiang Mai, Thailand	2006-2010

HONORS AND AWARDS

•	Abroad fellowship from the Institute for the Promotion of Teaching Science and Technology Project (DPST),	2013-2018
	Ministry of Education, Thailand	
•	Scholarship from Development and Promotion of Science and Technology Talents Project (DPST),	2003-2013
	Ministry of Education, Thailand	
•	Scholarship from Junior Scientist Talent Project (JSTP), Thailand	2007

SKILLS

■ Computer Language Python